Privacy Policy of **leadconvertpro.com**
========================================

Leadconvertpro.com collects some Personal Data from its Users.

Users may be subject to different protection standards and broader standards may therefore apply to some. Users can contact the Owner, to learn more about such standards.

This document contains [a section dedicated to Users in the European Union and their privacy rights](#cookie_policy_further_information).

This document contains [a section dedicated to Users in the United States and their privacy rights.](#all_us_laws_info)

This document can be printed for reference by using the print command in the settings of any browser.

Owner and Data Controller
-------------------------

Lead Convert Pro - 11023 Mustang Spring San Antonio, TX 78254

**Owner contact email:** contact@leadconvertpro.com

Types of Data collected
-----------------------

Among the types of Personal Data that leadconvertpro.com collects, by itself or through third parties, there are: first name; last name; phone number; company name; physical address; country; state; email address; ZIP/Postal code; city; website; Tracker; Usage Data; billing address; payment info; Data communicated while using the service; various types of Data; unique device identifiers for advertising (Google Advertiser ID or IDFA, for example); date of birth; gender; marital status; profession; geographic position; username; password; VAT Number; purchase history; device information; screenshots; workplace; picture; User ID.

Complete details on each type of Personal Data collected are provided in the dedicated sections of this privacy policy or by specific explanation texts displayed prior to the Data collection.  
Personal Data may be freely provided by the User, or, in case of Usage Data, collected automatically when using leadconvertpro.com.  
Unless specified otherwise, all Data requested by leadconvertpro.com is mandatory and failure to provide this Data may make it impossible for leadconvertpro.com to provide its services. In cases where leadconvertpro.com specifically states that some Data is not mandatory, Users are free not to communicate this Data without consequences to the availability or the functioning of the Service.  
Users who are uncertain about which Personal Data is mandatory are welcome to contact the Owner.  
Any use of Cookies – or of other tracking tools — by leadconvertpro.com or by the owners of third-party services used by leadconvertpro.com serves the purpose of providing the Service required by the User, in addition to any other purposes described in the present document and in the Cookie Policy.

Users are responsible for any third-party Personal Data obtained, published or shared through leadconvertpro.com.

Mode and place of processing the Data
-------------------------------------

### Methods of processing

The Owner takes appropriate security measures to prevent unauthorized access, disclosure, modification, or unauthorized destruction of the Data.  
The Data processing is carried out using computers and/or IT enabled tools, following organizational procedures and modes strictly related to the purposes indicated. In addition to the Owner, in some cases, the Data may be accessible to certain types of persons in charge, involved with the operation of leadconvertpro.com (administration, sales, marketing, legal, system administration) or external parties (such as third-party technical service providers, mail carriers, hosting providers, IT companies, communications agencies) appointed, if necessary, as Data Processors by the Owner. The updated list of these parties may be requested from the Owner at any time.

### Place

The Data is processed at the Owner's operating offices and in any other places where the parties involved in the processing are located.  
  
Depending on the User's location, data transfers may involve transferring the User's Data to a country other than their own. To find out more about the place of processing of such transferred Data, Users can check the section containing details about the processing of Personal Data.

### Retention time

Unless specified otherwise in this document, Personal Data shall be processed and stored for as long as required by the purpose they have been collected for and may be retained for longer due to applicable legal obligation or based on the Users’ consent.

The purposes of processing
--------------------------

The Data concerning the User is collected to allow the Owner to provide its Service, comply with its legal obligations, respond to enforcement requests, protect its rights and interests (or those of its Users or third parties), detect any malicious or fraudulent activity, as well as the following: Contacting the User, Access to third-party accounts, Interaction with external social networks and platforms, Analytics, Displaying content from external platforms, Tag Management, Platform services and hosting, Registration and authentication, Remarketing and behavioral targeting, Advertising, Managing data collection and online surveys, Interaction with live chat platforms, Communication, Connecting Data, Content commenting, Data transfer outside of the UK, Data transfer outside the EU, Handling payments, Heat mapping and session recording, Hosting and backend infrastructure, Handling activities related to productivity, Managing contacts and sending messages, Social features, SPAM protection and Traffic optimization and distribution.

For specific information about the Personal Data used for each purpose, the User may refer to the section “Detailed information on the processing of Personal Data”.

Facebook permissions asked by leadconvertpro.com
------------------------------------------------

Leadconvertpro.com may ask for some Facebook permissions allowing it to perform actions with the User's Facebook account and to retrieve information, including Personal Data, from it. This service allows leadconvertpro.com to connect with the User's account on the Facebook social network, provided by Facebook Inc.

For more information about the following permissions, refer to the [Facebook permissions documentation](https://developers.facebook.com/docs/facebook-login/permissions) and to the [Facebook privacy policy](https://www.facebook.com/about/privacy/).

The permissions asked are the following:

### Basic information

By default, this includes certain User’s Data such as id, name, picture, gender, and their locale. Certain connections of the User, such as the Friends, are also available. If the User has made more of their Data public, more information will be available.

### Manage Pages

Enables the application to retrieve access\_tokens for Pages and Applications that the User administrates.

### Managing Page Advertisements

Allows managing advertisements associated with the Page.

### Pages manage instant articles

Allows managing Instant Articles on behalf of Facebook Pages administered by the User.

### Pages manage posts

Allows the creation, editing and deletion of the User’s Page posts.

### Publish as Page

Enables the ability to post, comment and like as any of the Pages managed by the User.

### Read Mailbox

Provides the ability to read from a user's Facebook Inbox.

### Video upload

Add or modify User's videos.

### Website

Provides access to the User's web site URL.

Detailed information on the processing of Personal Data
-------------------------------------------------------

Personal Data is collected for the following purposes and using the following services:

* ### Access to third-party accounts
    
    This type of service allows leadconvertpro.com to access Data from your account on a third-party service and perform actions with it.  
    These services are not activated automatically, but require explicit authorization by the User.
    
    #### Facebook account access (Facebook, Inc.)
    
    This service allows leadconvertpro.com to connect with the User's account on the Facebook social network, provided by Facebook, Inc.
    
    Permissions asked: Manage Pages; Managing Page Advertisements; Pages manage instant articles; Pages manage posts; Publish as Page; Read Mailbox; Video upload; Website.
    
    Place of processing: United States – [Privacy Policy](https://www.facebook.com/policy.php).
    
    Category of Personal Information collected according to the CCPA: internet or other electronic network activity information; audio, electronic, visual, thermal, olfactory, or similar information.
    
    This processing constitutes:
    
* ### Advertising
    
    This type of service allows User Data to be utilized for advertising communication purposes. These communications are displayed in the form of banners and other advertisements on leadconvertpro.com, possibly based on User interests.  
    This does not mean that all Personal Data are used for this purpose. Information and conditions of use are shown below.  
    Some of the services listed below may use Trackers to identify Users or they may use the behavioral retargeting technique, i.e. displaying ads tailored to the User’s interests and behavior, including those detected outside leadconvertpro.com. For more information, please check the privacy policies of the relevant services.  
    Services of this kind usually offer the possibility to opt out of such tracking. In addition to any opt-out feature offered by any of the services below, Users may learn more on how to generally opt out of interest-based advertising within the dedicated section "How to opt-out of interest-based advertising" in this document.
    
    #### Facebook Lookalike Audience
    
    Facebook Lookalike Audience is an advertising and behavioral targeting service provided by Facebook, Inc. or by Facebook Ireland Ltd, depending on how the Owner manages the Data processing, that uses Data collected through Facebook Custom Audience in order to display ads to Users with similar behavior to Users who are already in a Custom Audience list on the base of their past use of leadconvertpro.com or engagement with relevant content across the Facebook apps and services.  
    On the base of these Data, personalized ads will be shown to Users suggested by Facebook Lookalike Audience.
    
    Users can opt out of Facebook's use of cookies for ads personalization by visiting this [opt-out page](https://www.aboutads.info/choices/).
    
    Personal Data processed: Tracker; Usage Data.
    
    Place of processing: United States – [Privacy Policy](https://www.facebook.com/about/privacy/) – [Opt Out](https://www.aboutads.info/choices/); Ireland – [Privacy Policy](https://www.facebook.com/about/privacy/) – [Opt Out](https://www.aboutads.info/choices/).
    
    Category of Personal Information collected according to the CCPA: internet or other electronic network activity information.
    
    This processing constitutes:
    
    * a Sale in California
    * a Sharing in California
    
    #### Meta ads conversion tracking (Meta pixel)
    
    Meta ads conversion tracking (Meta pixel) is an analytics service provided by Meta Platforms, Inc. or by Meta Platforms Ireland Limited, depending on how the Owner manages the Data processing, that connects data from the Meta Audience Network with actions performed on leadconvertpro.com. The Meta pixel tracks conversions that can be attributed to ads on Facebook, Instagram and Meta Audience Network.
    
    Personal Data processed: Trackers; Usage Data.
    
    Place of processing: United States – [Privacy Policy](https://www.facebook.com/about/privacy/) – [Opt out](https://www.facebook.com/adpreferences/ad_settings); Ireland – [Privacy Policy](https://www.facebook.com/about/privacy/) – [Opt out](https://www.facebook.com/adpreferences/ad_settings).
    
    Category of Personal Information collected according to the CCPA: internet or other electronic network activity information.
    
    This processing constitutes:
    
    * a Sale in California
    
    #### Facebook Audience Network
    
    Facebook Audience Network is an advertising service provided by Facebook, Inc. or by Facebook Ireland Ltd, depending on how the Owner manages the Data processing, **In order to understand Facebook's use of Data, consult [Facebook's data policy](https://www.facebook.com/about/privacy/).**
    
    Leadconvertpro.com may use identifiers for mobile devices (including Android Advertising ID or Advertising Identifier for iOS, respectively) and technologies similar to cookies to run the Facebook Audience Network service. One of the ways Audience Network shows ads is by using the User's ad preferences. The User can control this in the [Facebook ad settings](https://www.facebook.com/ads/settings).
    
    Users may opt-out of certain Audience Network targeting through applicable device settings, such as the device advertising settings for mobile phones or by following the instructions in other Audience Network related sections of this privacy policy, if available.
    
    Personal Data processed: Tracker; unique device identifiers for advertising (Google Advertiser ID or IDFA, for example); Usage Data.
    
    Place of processing: United States – [Privacy Policy](https://www.facebook.com/about/privacy/) – [Opt Out](https://www.facebook.com/settings?tab=ads); Ireland – [Privacy Policy](https://www.facebook.com/about/privacy/) – [Opt Out](https://www.facebook.com/settings?tab=ads).
    
    Category of Personal Information collected according to the CCPA: identifiers; internet or other electronic network activity information.
    
    This processing constitutes:
    
    * a Sale in California
    * a Sharing in California
    
    #### ShareThis (Sharethis Inc.)
    
    ShareThis is an advertising and behavioral targeting service provided by Sharethis Inc. that displays a widget that allows interaction with social networks and external platforms as well as sharing the contents of leadconvertpro.com. Users can opt out of ShareThis's use of Trackers for ads personalization by visiting this [opt-out page](https://sharethis.com/privacy/).
    
    Personal Data processed: Tracker; Usage Data.
    
    Place of processing: United States – [Privacy Policy](https://sharethis.com/privacy/) – [Opt out](https://sharethis.com/privacy/).
    
    Category of Personal Information collected according to the CCPA: internet or other electronic network activity information.
    
    This processing constitutes:
    
    * a Sale in California
    * a Sharing in California
    
* ### Analytics
    
    The services contained in this section enable the Owner to monitor and analyze web traffic and can be used to keep track of User behavior.
    
    #### Google Analytics (Universal Analytics)
    
    Google Analytics (Universal Analytics) is a web analysis service provided by Google LLC or by Google Ireland Limited, depending on how the Owner manages the Data processing, (“Google”). Google utilizes the Data collected to track and examine the use of leadconvertpro.com, to prepare reports on its activities and share them with other Google services.  
    Google may use the Data collected to contextualize and personalize the ads of its own advertising network.
    
    In order to understand Google's use of Data, consult [Google's partner policy](https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/).
    
    Personal Data processed: Tracker; Usage Data.
    
    Place of processing: United States – [Privacy Policy](https://business.safety.google/privacy/) – [Opt Out](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en); Ireland – [Privacy Policy](https://business.safety.google/privacy/) – [Opt Out](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en).
    
    Category of Personal Information collected according to the CCPA: internet or other electronic network activity information.
    
    This processing constitutes:
    
    * a Sale in the United States
    
    #### Google Analytics (Universal Analytics) with anonymized IP
    
    Google Analytics (Universal Analytics) is a web analysis service provided by Google LLC or by Google Ireland Limited, depending on how the Owner manages the Data processing, (“Google”). Google utilizes the Data collected to track and examine the use of leadconvertpro.com, to prepare reports on its activities and share them with other Google services.  
    Google may use the Data collected to contextualize and personalize the ads of its own advertising network.  
    This integration of Google Analytics anonymizes your IP address. It works by shortening Users' IP addresses within member states of the European Union or in other contracting states to the Agreement on the European Economic Area. Only in exceptional cases will the complete IP address be sent to a Google server and shortened within the US.
    
    In order to understand Google's use of Data, consult [Google's partner policy](https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/).
    
    Personal Data processed: Tracker; Usage Data.
    
    Place of processing: United States – [Privacy Policy](https://business.safety.google/privacy/) – [Opt Out](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en); Ireland – [Privacy Policy](https://business.safety.google/privacy/) – [Opt Out](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en).
    
    Category of Personal Information collected according to the CCPA: internet or other electronic network activity information.
    
    This processing constitutes:
    
    * a Sale in California
    
    #### Wordpress Stats
    
    Wordpress Stats is an analytics service provided by Automattic Inc. or by Aut O’Mattic A8C Ireland Ltd., depending on how the Owner manages the Data processing.
    
    Personal Data processed: Tracker; Usage Data.
    
    Place of processing: United States – [Privacy Policy](https://automattic.com/privacy/); Ireland – [Privacy Policy](https://automattic.com/privacy/).
    
    Category of Personal Information collected according to the CCPA: internet or other electronic network activity information.
    
    This processing constitutes:
    
    * a Sale in California
    
    #### Facebook Analytics for Apps
    
    Facebook Analytics for Apps is an analytics service provided by Facebook, Inc. or by Facebook Ireland Ltd, depending on how the Owner manages the Data processing,
    
    Personal Data processed: Tracker; Usage Data; various types of Data as specified in the privacy policy of the service.
    
    Place of processing: United States – [Privacy Policy](https://www.facebook.com/about/privacy/); Ireland – [Privacy Policy](https://www.facebook.com/about/privacy/).
    
    Category of Personal Information collected according to the CCPA: internet or other electronic network activity information.
    
    This processing constitutes:
    
    * a Sale in California
    
    #### Google Analytics Advertising Reporting Features
    
    Google Analytics on leadconvertpro.com has Advertising Reporting Features activated, which collects additional information from the DoubleClick cookie (web activity) and from device advertising IDs (app activity). It allows the Owner to analyze specific behavior and interests Data (traffic Data and Users' ads interaction Data) and, if enabled, demographic Data (information about the age and gender).
    
    Users can opt out of Google's use of cookies by visiting Google's [Ads Settings](https://adssettings.google.com/authenticated).
    
    Personal Data processed: Tracker; unique device identifiers for advertising (Google Advertiser ID or IDFA, for example); various types of Data as specified in the privacy policy of the service.
    
    Place of processing: United States – [Privacy Policy](https://policies.google.com/privacy) – [Opt Out](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout); Ireland – [Privacy Policy](https://policies.google.com/privacy) – [Opt Out](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout).
    
    Category of Personal Information collected according to the CCPA: identifiers; internet or other electronic network activity information.
    
    This processing constitutes:
    
    * a Sale in California
    
    #### Google Analytics Demographics and Interests reports
    
    Google Analytics Demographics and Interests reports is a Google Advertising Reporting feature that makes available demographic and interests Data inside Google Analytics for leadconvertpro.com (demographics means age and gender Data).
    
    Users can opt out of Google's use of cookies by visiting Google's [Ads Settings](https://adssettings.google.com/authenticated).
    
    Personal Data processed: Tracker; unique device identifiers for advertising (Google Advertiser ID or IDFA, for example).
    
    Place of processing: United States – [Privacy Policy](https://policies.google.com/privacy) – [Opt Out](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout); Ireland – [Privacy Policy](https://policies.google.com/privacy) – [Opt Out](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout).
    
    Category of Personal Information collected according to the CCPA: identifiers; internet or other electronic network activity information.
    
    This processing constitutes:
    
    * a Sale in California
    
    #### Analytics collected directly (leadconvertpro.com)
    
    Leadconvertpro.com uses an internal analytics system that does not involve third parties.
    
    Personal Data processed: Tracker; Usage Data.
    
    Category of Personal Information collected according to the CCPA: internet or other electronic network activity information.
    
    This processing constitutes:
    
    #### YouTube Analytics and Reporting API
    
    YouTube Analytics and Reporting API is a video content analytics service provided by Google LLC or by Google Ireland Limited, depending on how the Owner manages the Data processing.
    
    Through this Service, leadconvertpro.com may collect Data directly or indirectly on or from Users’ devices, including by making use of trackers. Users may restrict such access to their Data via the [security settings page](https://security.google.com/settings/security/permissions) provided by Google. Users may ask the Owner for further information about these privacy settings at any time through the contact details provided in this document.
    
    Data collected through the Service may also be used to help third parties deliver interest-based advertising. Users can opt out of third-party interest-based advertising through their device settings or by visiting the [Network Advertising Initiative opt-out page](http://optout.networkadvertising.org/?c=1).
    
    Personal Data processed: Data communicated while using the service; device information; Tracker; Usage Data; User ID; username.
    
    Place of processing: United States – [Privacy Policy](http://www.google.com/policies/privacy) – [Opt out](https://security.google.com/settings/security/permissions); Ireland – [Privacy Policy](http://www.google.com/policies/privacy) – [Opt out](https://security.google.com/settings/security/permissions).
    
    Category of Personal Information collected according to the CCPA: identifiers; internet or other electronic network activity information.
    
    This processing constitutes:
    
    * a Sale in California
    
* ### Communication
    
    #### Chat Widget
    
    A widget used on our website to communicate with visitors through chat and SMS text messages. Information will be pushed and stored to https://app.leadconvertpro.com
    
    This processing constitutes:
    
    * a Sharing in California
    
* ### Connecting Data
    
    This type of service allows the Owner to connect Data with third-party services disclosed within this privacy policy.  
    This results in Data flowing through these services, potentially causing the retention of this Data.
    
    #### Zapier (Zapier, Inc.)
    
    Zapier is a workflow automation service provided by Zapier, Inc. that automates the movement of Data between (third-party) services.
    
    Personal Data processed: city; company name; country; Data communicated while using the service; email address; first name; geographic position; last name; password; phone number; Tracker; username; VAT Number; ZIP/Postal code.
    
    Place of processing: United States – [Privacy Policy](https://zapier.com/privacy/).
    
    Category of Personal Information collected according to the CCPA: identifiers; commercial information; internet or other electronic network activity information; geolocation data.
    
    This processing constitutes:
    
    * a Sale in California
    
* ### Contacting the User
    
    #### Contact form (leadconvertpro.com)
    
    By filling in the contact form with their Data, the User authorizes leadconvertpro.com to use these details to reply to requests for information, quotes or any other kind of request as indicated by the form’s header.
    
    Personal Data processed: city; company name; country; email address; first name; last name; phone number; physical address; state; website; ZIP/Postal code.
    
    Category of Personal Information collected according to the CCPA: identifiers; commercial information; internet or other electronic network activity information.
    
    This processing constitutes:
    
    * a Sale in California
    
    #### Mailing list or newsletter (leadconvertpro.com)
    
    By registering on the mailing list or for the newsletter, the User’s email address will be added to the contact list of those who may receive email messages containing information of commercial or promotional nature concerning leadconvertpro.com. Your email address might also be added to this list as a result of signing up to leadconvertpro.com or after making a purchase.
    
    Personal Data processed: city; company name; country; email address; first name; last name; phone number; physical address; state; website; ZIP/Postal code.
    
    Category of Personal Information collected according to the CCPA: identifiers; commercial information; internet or other electronic network activity information.
    
    This processing constitutes:
    
    * a Sale in Virginia, Colorado, Connecticut, Utah, Texas, Oregon, Nevada, Delaware, Iowa, New Hampshire, New Jersey, Nebraska and Montana
    
    #### Phone contact (leadconvertpro.com)
    
    Users that provided their phone number might be contacted for commercial or promotional purposes related to leadconvertpro.com, as well as for fulfilling support requests.
    
    Personal Data processed: phone number.
    
    Category of Personal Information collected according to the CCPA: identifiers.
    
    This processing constitutes:
    
* ### Content commenting
    
    Content commenting services allow Users to make and publish their comments on the contents of leadconvertpro.com.  
    Depending on the settings chosen by the Owner, Users may also leave anonymous comments. If there is an email address among the Personal Data provided by the User, it may be used to send notifications of comments on the same content. Users are responsible for the content of their own comments.  
    If a content commenting service provided by third parties is installed, it may still collect web traffic data for the pages where the comment service is installed, even when Users do not use the content commenting service.
    
    #### Comment system managed directly (leadconvertpro.com)
    
    Leadconvertpro.com has its own internal content comment system.
    
    Personal Data processed: email address; first name; last name.
    
    Category of Personal Information collected according to the CCPA: identifiers.
    
    This processing constitutes:
    
    * a Sale in Virginia, Colorado, Connecticut, Utah, Texas, Oregon, Nevada, Delaware, Iowa, New Hampshire, New Jersey, Nebraska and Montana
    * Targeted Advertising in Virginia, Colorado, Connecticut, Utah, Texas, Oregon, Nevada, Delaware, Iowa, New Hampshire, New Jersey, Nebraska and Montana
    
* ### Displaying content from external platforms
    
    This type of service allows you to view content hosted on external platforms directly from the pages of leadconvertpro.com and interact with them.  
    This type of service might still collect web traffic data for the pages where the service is installed, even when Users do not use it.
    
    #### Google Fonts
    
    Google Fonts is a typeface visualization service provided by Google LLC or by Google Ireland Limited, depending on how the Owner manages the Data processing, that allows leadconvertpro.com to incorporate content of this kind on its pages.
    
    Personal Data processed: Usage Data; various types of Data as specified in the privacy policy of the service.
    
    Place of processing: United States – [Privacy Policy](https://policies.google.com/privacy); Ireland – [Privacy Policy](https://policies.google.com/privacy).
    
    Category of Personal Information collected according to the CCPA: internet or other electronic network activity information.
    
    This processing constitutes:
    
    * a Sale in California
    
    #### Gravatar
    
    Gravatar is an image visualization service provided by Automattic Inc. or by Aut O’Mattic A8C Ireland Ltd., depending on how the Owner manages the Data processing, that allows leadconvertpro.com to incorporate content of this kind on its pages.  
    Please note that if Gravatar images are used for comment forms, the commenter's email address or parts of it may be sent to Gravatar - even if the commenter has not signed up for that service.
    
    Personal Data processed: email address; Usage Data.
    
    Place of processing: United States – [Privacy Policy](https://automattic.com/privacy/); Ireland – [Privacy Policy](https://automattic.com/privacy/).
    
    Category of Personal Information collected according to the CCPA: identifiers; internet or other electronic network activity information.
    
    This processing constitutes:
    
    * a Sale in California
    
* ### Handling activities related to productivity
    
    This type of service helps the Owner to manage tasks, collaboration and, in general, activities related to productivity. In using this type of service, Data of Users will be processed and may be retained, depending on the purpose of the activity in question.  
    These services may be integrated with a wide range of third-party services disclosed within this privacy policy to enable the Owner to import or export Data needed for the relative activity.
    
    #### Feedbear
    
    Platform used for Changelog and Roadmap. Visitors can upvote and add software recommendations.
    
    This processing constitutes:
    
    * a Sharing in California
    
    #### Gmail
    
    Gmail is a service that manages email communication provided by Google LLC or by Google Ireland Limited, depending on how the Owner manages the Data processing. Such email communication is not scanned by Google for advertising purposes. In addition, Google does not collect or use data inside this service for advertising purposes in any other way.
    
    Personal Data processed: city; company name; country; Data communicated while using the service; date of birth; email address; first name; geographic position; last name; password; phone number; physical address; screenshots; Tracker; username; VAT Number; workplace.
    
    Place of processing: United States – [Privacy Policy](https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/); Ireland – [Privacy Policy](https://policies.google.com/privacy).
    
    Category of Personal Information collected according to the CCPA: identifiers; commercial information; internet or other electronic network activity information; geolocation data; employment related information.
    
    This processing constitutes:
    
    * a Sale in California
    
* ### Handling payments
    
    Unless otherwise specified, leadconvertpro.com processes any payments by credit card, bank transfer or other means via external payment service providers. In general and unless where otherwise stated, Users are requested to provide their payment details and personal information directly to such payment service providers. Leadconvertpro.com isn't involved in the collection and processing of such information: instead, it will only receive a notification by the relevant payment service provider as to whether payment has been successfully completed.
    
    #### PayPal (PayPal Inc.)
    
    PayPal is a payment service provided by PayPal Inc., which allows Users to make online payments.
    
    Personal Data processed: billing address; device information; email address; first name; last name; password; payment info; phone number; purchase history; Tracker; Usage Data; username; various types of Data as specified in the privacy policy of the service.
    
    Place of processing: See the PayPal privacy policy – [Privacy Policy](https://www.paypal.com/webapps/mpp/ua/privacy-full).
    
    Category of Personal Information collected according to the CCPA: identifiers; commercial information; internet or other electronic network activity information.
    
    This processing constitutes:
    
    * a Sale in Virginia, Colorado, Connecticut, Utah, Texas, Oregon, Nevada, Delaware, Iowa, New Hampshire, New Jersey, Nebraska and Montana
    
    #### Stripe (Stripe Inc)
    
    Stripe is a payment service provided by Stripe Inc.
    
    Personal Data processed: billing address; email address; first name; last name; payment info; purchase history; Tracker; Usage Data; various types of Data as specified in the privacy policy of the service.
    
    Place of processing: United States – [Privacy Policy](https://stripe.com/gb/privacy).
    
    Category of Personal Information collected according to the CCPA: identifiers; commercial information; internet or other electronic network activity information.
    
    This processing constitutes:
    
* ### Heat mapping and session recording
    
    Heat mapping services are used to display the areas of leadconvertpro.com that Users interact with most frequently. This shows where the points of interest are. These services make it possible to monitor and analyze web traffic and keep track of User behavior.  
    Some of these services may record sessions and make them available for later visual playback.
    
    #### Hotjar Heat Maps & Recordings (Hotjar Ltd.)
    
    Hotjar is a session recording and heat mapping service provided by Hotjar Ltd.  
    Hotjar honors generic „Do Not Track” headers. This means the browser can tell its script not to collect any of the User's data. This is a setting that is available in all major browsers. Find Hotjar’s [opt-out information here](https://www.hotjar.com/legal/compliance/opt-out).
    
    Personal Data processed: Tracker; Usage Data; various types of Data as specified in the privacy policy of the service.
    
    Place of processing: Malta – [Privacy Policy](https://www.hotjar.com/legal/policies/privacy) – [Opt Out](https://www.hotjar.com/legal/compliance/opt-out).
    
    Category of Personal Information collected according to the CCPA: internet or other electronic network activity information.
    
    This processing constitutes:
    
    * a Sale in California
    
* ### Hosting and backend infrastructure
    
    This type of service has the purpose of hosting Data and files that enable leadconvertpro.com to run and be distributed as well as to provide a ready-made infrastructure to run specific features or parts of leadconvertpro.com.
    
    Some services among those listed below, if any, may work through geographically distributed servers, making it difficult to determine the actual location where the Personal Data are stored.
    
    #### iubenda Consent Solution (iubenda srl)
    
    iubenda Consent Solution is a service that facilitates the collection and management of proofs of consent provided by iubenda srl.
    
    Personal Data processed: Data communicated while using the service; Tracker.
    
    Place of processing: Italy – [Privacy Policy](https://www.iubenda.com/privacy-policy/252372).
    
    Category of Personal Information collected according to the CCPA: internet or other electronic network activity information.
    
    This processing constitutes:
    
    #### Linode (Linode, LLC.)
    
    Linode is a hosting service provided by Linode, LLC.
    
    Personal Data processed: various types of Data as specified in the privacy policy of the service.
    
    Place of processing: United States – [Privacy Policy](https://www.linode.com/privacy).
    
    Category of Personal Information collected according to the CCPA: internet or other electronic network activity information.
    
    This processing constitutes:
    
* ### Interaction with external social networks and platforms
    
    This type of service allows interaction with social networks or other external platforms directly from the pages of leadconvertpro.com.  
    The interaction and information obtained through leadconvertpro.com are always subject to the User’s privacy settings for each social network.  
    This type of service might still collect traffic data for the pages where the service is installed, even when Users do not use it.  
    It is recommended to log out from the respective services in order to make sure that the processed data on leadconvertpro.com isn’t being connected back to the User’s profile.
    
    #### Facebook Like button and social widgets (Facebook, Inc.)
    
    The Facebook Like button and social widgets are services allowing interaction with the Facebook social network provided by Facebook, Inc.
    
    Personal Data processed: Tracker; Usage Data.
    
    Place of processing: United States – [Privacy Policy](https://www.facebook.com/privacy/explanation).
    
    Category of Personal Information collected according to the CCPA: internet or other electronic network activity information.
    
    This processing constitutes:
    
    * a Sale in the United States
    
    #### LinkedIn button and social widgets (LinkedIn Corporation)
    
    The LinkedIn button and social widgets are services allowing interaction with the LinkedIn social network provided by LinkedIn Corporation.
    
    Personal Data processed: Tracker; Usage Data.
    
    Place of processing: United States – [Privacy Policy](https://www.linkedin.com/legal/privacy-policy).
    
    Category of Personal Information collected according to the CCPA: internet or other electronic network activity information.
    
    This processing constitutes:
    
    * a Sale in California
    
    #### Twitter Tweet button and social widgets (X Corp.)
    
    The Twitter Tweet button and social widgets are services allowing interaction with the Twitter social network provided by Twitter, Inc.
    
    Personal Data processed: Tracker; Usage Data.
    
    Place of processing: United States – [Privacy Policy](https://twitter.com/en/privacy).
    
    Category of Personal Information collected according to the CCPA: internet or other electronic network activity information.
    
    This processing constitutes:
    
    * a Sale in California
    
* ### Interaction with live chat platforms
    
    This type of service allows Users to interact with third-party live chat platforms directly from the pages of leadconvertpro.com, in order to contact and be contacted by leadconvertpro.com‘s support service.  
    If one of these services is installed, it may collect browsing and Usage Data in the pages where it is installed, even if the Users do not actively use the service. Moreover, live chat conversations may be logged.
    
    #### Facebook Messenger Customer Chat
    
    The Facebook Messenger Customer Chat is a service for interacting with the Facebook Messenger live chat platform provided by Facebook, Inc. or by Facebook Ireland Ltd, depending on how the Owner manages the Data processing,
    
    Personal Data processed: Data communicated while using the service; Tracker; Usage Data.
    
    Place of processing: United States – [Privacy Policy](https://www.facebook.com/about/privacy/); Ireland – [Privacy Policy](https://www.facebook.com/about/privacy/).
    
    Category of Personal Information collected according to the CCPA: internet or other electronic network activity information.
    
    This processing constitutes:
    
    * a Sale in California
    
* ### Managing contacts and sending messages
    
    This type of service makes it possible to manage a database of email contacts, phone contacts or any other contact information to communicate with the User.  
    These services may also collect data concerning the date and time when the message was viewed by the User, as well as when the User interacted with it, such as by clicking on links included in the message.
    
    #### Twilio (Twilio, Inc.)
    
    Twilio is a phone numbers management and communication service provided by Twilio, Inc.
    
    Personal Data processed: phone number.
    
    Place of processing: United States – [Privacy Policy](https://www.twilio.com/legal/privacy).
    
    Category of Personal Information collected according to the CCPA: identifiers.
    
    This processing constitutes:
    
    * a Sale in California
    * a Sharing in California
    
    #### Lead Convert Pro Lead Management
    
    Lead Convert Pro is a lead management software application used to communicate with new and existing clients through SMS, Email, Phone, Facebook Messenger, Google Messaging, and voicemail drops.
    
    This processing constitutes:
    
    * a Sharing in California
    
* ### Managing data collection and online surveys
    
    This type of service allows leadconvertpro.com to manage the creation, deployment, administration, distribution and analysis of online forms and surveys in order to collect, save and reuse Data from any responding Users.  
    The Personal Data collected depend on the information asked and provided by the Users in the corresponding online form.
    
    These services may be integrated with a wide range of third-party services to enable the Owner to take subsequent steps with the Data processed - e.g. managing contacts, sending messages, analytics, advertising and payment processing.
    
    #### Facebook lead ads
    
    Facebook lead ads is an advertising and data collection service provided by Facebook, Inc. or by Facebook Ireland Ltd, depending on how the Owner manages the Data processing, that allows form-based ads to be shown to Users pre-populated with Personal Data from their Facebook profiles, such as names and email addresses. Depending on the type of advertisement, Users may be requested to provide further information.
    
    Form submission results in the collection and processing of these Data by the Owner under this privacy policy, and only for the specific purpose outlined on the form and/or inside this privacy policy, where provided.
    
    Users may exercise their rights, at any time, including the right to withdraw their consent to the processing of their Data, as specified in the section containing information about User rights in this privacy policy.
    
    Personal Data processed: city; company name; country; Data communicated while using the service; date of birth; email address; first name; gender; last name; marital status; phone number; physical address; profession; state; Tracker; Usage Data; ZIP/Postal code.
    
    Place of processing: United States – [Privacy Policy](https://www.facebook.com/about/privacy/) – [Opt out](https://www.facebook.com/ads/preferences/?entry_product=ad_settings_screen); Ireland – [Privacy Policy](https://www.facebook.com/about/privacy/) – [Opt out](https://www.facebook.com/ads/preferences/?entry_product=ad_settings_screen).
    
    Category of Personal Information collected according to the CCPA: identifiers; commercial information; biometric information; internet or other electronic network activity information; employment related information; inferences drawn from other personal information.
    
    This processing constitutes:
    
    * a Sale in California
    
* ### Platform services and hosting
    
    These services have the purpose of hosting and running key components of leadconvertpro.com, therefore allowing the provision of leadconvertpro.com from within a unified platform. Such platforms provide a wide range of tools to the Owner – e.g. analytics, user registration, commenting, database management, e-commerce, payment processing – that imply the collection and handling of Personal Data.  
    Some of these services work through geographically distributed servers, making it difficult to determine the actual location where the Personal Data are stored.
    
    #### WordPress.com
    
    WordPress.com is a platform provided by Automattic Inc. or by Aut O’Mattic A8C Ireland Ltd., depending on how the Owner manages the Data processing, that allows the Owner to build, run and host leadconvertpro.com.
    
    Personal Data processed: billing address; Data communicated while using the service; email address; first name; last name; payment info; phone number; Tracker; Usage Data; various types of Data as specified in the privacy policy of the service.
    
    Place of processing: United States – [Privacy Policy](https://automattic.com/privacy/); Ireland – [Privacy Policy](https://automattic.com/privacy/).
    
    Category of Personal Information collected according to the CCPA: identifiers; commercial information; internet or other electronic network activity information.
    
    This processing constitutes:
    
* ### Registration and authentication
    
    By registering or authenticating, Users allow leadconvertpro.com to identify them and give them access to dedicated services.  
    Depending on what is described below, third parties may provide registration and authentication services. In this case, leadconvertpro.com will be able to access some Data, stored by these third-party services, for registration or identification purposes.  
    Some of the services listed below may also collect Personal Data for targeting and profiling purposes; to find out more, please refer to the description of each service.
    
    #### WordPress.com Single Sign On
    
    WordPress.com Single Sign On is a registration and authentication service provided by Automattic Inc. or by Aut O’Mattic A8C Ireland Ltd., depending on how the Owner manages the Data processing, and is connected to the WordPress.com network.
    
    Personal Data processed: Tracker; various types of Data as specified in the privacy policy of the service.
    
    Place of processing: United States – [Privacy Policy](https://automattic.com/privacy/); Ireland – [Privacy Policy](https://automattic.com/privacy/).
    
    Category of Personal Information collected according to the CCPA: internet or other electronic network activity information.
    
    This processing constitutes:
    
    * a Sale in California
    
    #### Facebook Authentication
    
    Facebook Authentication is a registration and authentication service provided by Facebook, Inc. or by Facebook Ireland Ltd, depending on how the Owner manages the Data processing, and is connected to the Facebook social network.
    
    Personal Data processed: Tracker; various types of Data as specified in the privacy policy of the service.
    
    Place of processing: United States – [Privacy Policy](https://www.facebook.com/help/405977429438260); Ireland – [Privacy Policy](https://www.facebook.com/help/405977429438260).
    
    Category of Personal Information collected according to the CCPA: internet or other electronic network activity information.
    
    This processing constitutes:
    
    * a Sale in California
    
    #### Facebook Oauth
    
    Facebook Oauth is a registration and authentication service provided by Facebook, Inc. or by Facebook Ireland Ltd, depending on how the Owner manages the Data processing, and is connected to the Facebook social network.
    
    Personal Data processed: Tracker; various types of Data.
    
    Place of processing: United States – [Privacy Policy](https://www.facebook.com/policy.php); Ireland – [Privacy Policy](https://www.facebook.com/policy.php).
    
    Category of Personal Information collected according to the CCPA: internet or other electronic network activity information.
    
    This processing constitutes:
    
    * a Sale in California
    
* ### Remarketing and behavioral targeting
    
    This type of service allows leadconvertpro.com and its partners to inform, optimize and serve advertising based on past use of leadconvertpro.com by the User.  
    This activity is facilitated by tracking Usage Data and by using Trackers to collect information which is then transferred to the partners that manage the remarketing and behavioral targeting activity.  
    Some services offer a remarketing option based on email address lists.  
    In addition to any opt-out feature provided by any of the services below, Users may opt out by visiting the [Network Advertising Initiative opt-out page](http://optout.networkadvertising.org/?c=1).
    
    **Users may also opt-out of certain advertising features through applicable device settings, such as the device advertising settings for mobile phones or ads settings in general**.
    
    #### Facebook Remarketing
    
    Facebook Remarketing is a remarketing and behavioral targeting service provided by Facebook, Inc. or by Facebook Ireland Ltd, depending on how the Owner manages the Data processing, that connects the activity of leadconvertpro.com with the Facebook advertising network.
    
    Personal Data processed: Tracker; Usage Data.
    
    Place of processing: United States – [Privacy Policy](https://www.facebook.com/about/privacy/) – [Opt Out](https://www.aboutads.info/choices/); Ireland – [Privacy Policy](https://www.facebook.com/about/privacy/) – [Opt Out](https://www.aboutads.info/choices/).
    
    Category of Personal Information collected according to the CCPA: internet or other electronic network activity information.
    
    This processing constitutes:
    
    * a Sale in California
    * a Sharing in California
    
    #### Facebook Custom Audience
    
    Facebook Custom Audience is a remarketing and behavioral targeting service provided by Facebook, Inc. or by Facebook Ireland Ltd, depending on how the Owner manages the Data processing, that connects the activity of leadconvertpro.com with the Facebook advertising network.
    
    Users can opt out of Facebook's use of cookies for ads personalization by visiting this [opt-out page](https://www.aboutads.info/choices/).
    
    Personal Data processed: email address; Tracker.
    
    Place of processing: United States – [Privacy Policy](https://www.facebook.com/about/privacy/) – [Opt Out](https://www.aboutads.info/choices/); Ireland – [Privacy Policy](https://www.facebook.com/about/privacy/) – [Opt Out](https://www.aboutads.info/choices/).
    
    Category of Personal Information collected according to the CCPA: identifiers; internet or other electronic network activity information.
    
    This processing constitutes:
    
    * a Sale in California
    * a Sharing in California
    
    #### Remarketing with Google Analytics
    
    Remarketing with Google Analytics is a remarketing and behavioral targeting service provided by Google LLC or by Google Ireland Limited, depending on how the Owner manages the Data processing, that connects the tracking activity performed by Google Analytics and its Cookies with the Google Ads advertising network and the Doubleclick Cookie.
    
    Personal Data processed: Tracker; Usage Data.
    
    Place of processing: United States – [Privacy Policy](https://policies.google.com/privacy) – [Opt Out](https://adssettings.google.com/authenticated); Ireland – [Privacy Policy](https://policies.google.com/privacy) – [Opt Out](https://adssettings.google.com/authenticated#display_optout).
    
    Category of Personal Information collected according to the CCPA: internet or other electronic network activity information.
    
    This processing constitutes:
    
    * a Sale in California
    * a Sharing in California
    
    #### Google Signals
    
    Leadconvertpro.com uses Google Signals, a feature of Google Analytics, which will associate the visitation information that it collects from leadconvertpro.com with Google information from accounts of signed-in Google-account users who have consented to this association for the purpose of ads personalization. This Google information may include User location, search history, YouTube history and Data from sites that partner with Google – and is used to provide aggregated and anonymized insights into Users' cross device behaviors.
    
    If a User falls under the described association, they [may access and/or delete such Data via My Activity](https://myactivity.google.com/myactivity) provided by Google.
    
    Personal Data processed: Tracker; Usage Data.
    
    Place of processing: United States – [Privacy Policy](https://policies.google.com/privacy) – [Opt Out](https://adssettings.google.com/authenticated); Ireland – [Privacy Policy](https://policies.google.com/privacy) – [Opt Out](https://adssettings.google.com/authenticated).
    
    Category of Personal Information collected according to the CCPA: internet or other electronic network activity information.
    
    This processing constitutes:
    
    * a Sale in California
    * a Sharing in California
    
    #### Google Ads Remarketing
    
    Google Ads Remarketing is a remarketing and behavioral targeting service provided by Google LLC or by Google Ireland Limited, depending on how the Owner manages the Data processing, that connects the activity of leadconvertpro.com with the Google Ads advertising network and the DoubleClick Cookie.
    
    Users can opt out of Google's use of cookies for ads personalization by visiting Google's [Ads Settings](https://adssettings.google.com/authenticated).
    
    Personal Data processed: Tracker; Usage Data.
    
    Place of processing: United States – [Privacy Policy](https://policies.google.com/privacy) – [Opt Out](https://adssettings.google.com/authenticated); Ireland – [Privacy Policy](https://policies.google.com/privacy) – [Opt Out](https://adssettings.google.com/authenticated#display_optout).
    
    Category of Personal Information collected according to the CCPA: internet or other electronic network activity information.
    
    This processing constitutes:
    
    * a Sale in California
    * a Sharing in California
    
    #### LinkedIn Website Retargeting (LinkedIn Corporation)
    
    LinkedIn Website Retargeting is a remarketing and behavioral targeting service provided by LinkedIn Corporation that connects the activity of leadconvertpro.com with the LinkedIn advertising network.
    
    Personal Data processed: Tracker; Usage Data.
    
    Place of processing: United States – [Privacy Policy](https://www.linkedin.com/legal/privacy-policy) – [Opt Out](https://www.linkedin.com/legal/cookie_policy).
    
    Category of Personal Information collected according to the CCPA: internet or other electronic network activity information.
    
    This processing constitutes:
    
    * a Sale in California
    * a Sharing in California
    
    #### Twitter Remarketing (X Corp.)
    
    Twitter Remarketing is a remarketing and behavioral targeting service provided by Twitter, Inc. that connects the activity of leadconvertpro.com with the Twitter advertising network.
    
    Personal Data processed: Tracker; Usage Data.
    
    Place of processing: United States – [Privacy Policy](https://twitter.com/en/privacy).
    
    Category of Personal Information collected according to the CCPA: internet or other electronic network activity information.
    
    This processing constitutes:
    
    * a Sale in California
    * a Sharing in California
    
* ### Social features
    
    #### Inviting and suggesting friends (leadconvertpro.com)
    
    Leadconvertpro.com may use the Personal Data provided to allow Users to invite their friends - for example through the address book, if access has been provided - and to suggest friends or connections inside it.
    
    Personal Data processed: various types of Data.
    
    Category of Personal Information collected according to the CCPA: internet or other electronic network activity information.
    
    This processing constitutes:
    
    #### Public profile (leadconvertpro.com)
    
    Users may have public profiles that other Users can display. In addition to the Personal Data provided, this profile may contain Users' interactions with leadconvertpro.com.
    
    Personal Data processed: city; company name; country; email address; first name; gender; geographic position; last name; phone number; physical address; picture; profession; state; username.
    
    Category of Personal Information collected according to the CCPA: identifiers; commercial information; biometric information; geolocation data; audio, electronic, visual, thermal, olfactory, or similar information; employment related information.
    
    This processing constitutes:
    
* ### SPAM protection
    
    This type of service analyzes the traffic of leadconvertpro.com, potentially containing Users' Personal Data, with the purpose of filtering it from parts of traffic, messages and content that are recognized as SPAM.
    
    #### Google reCAPTCHA
    
    Google reCAPTCHA is a SPAM protection service provided by Google LLC or by Google Ireland Limited, depending on how the Owner manages the Data processing.  
    The use of reCAPTCHA is subject to the Google [privacy policy](https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/) and [terms of use](https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/terms/).
    
    In order to understand Google's use of Data, consult [Google's partner policy](https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/).
    
    Personal Data processed: Tracker; Usage Data.
    
    Place of processing: United States – [Privacy Policy](https://business.safety.google/privacy/); Ireland – [Privacy Policy](https://business.safety.google/privacy/).
    
    Category of Personal Information collected according to the CCPA: internet or other electronic network activity information.
    
    This processing constitutes:
    
* ### Tag Management
    
    This type of service helps the Owner to manage the tags or scripts needed on leadconvertpro.com in a centralized fashion.  
    This results in the Users' Data flowing through these services, potentially resulting in the retention of this Data.
    
    #### Google Tag Manager
    
    Google Tag Manager is a tag management service provided by Google LLC or by Google Ireland Limited, depending on how the Owner manages the Data processing.
    
    Personal Data processed: Tracker; Usage Data.
    
    Place of processing: United States – [Privacy Policy](https://policies.google.com/privacy); Ireland – [Privacy Policy](https://policies.google.com/privacy).
    
    Category of Personal Information collected according to the CCPA: internet or other electronic network activity information.
    
    This processing constitutes:
    
    * a Sale in California
    
* ### Traffic optimization and distribution
    
    This type of service allows leadconvertpro.com to distribute their content using servers located across different countries and to optimize their performance.  
    Which Personal Data are processed depends on the characteristics and the way these services are implemented. Their function is to filter communications between leadconvertpro.com and the User's browser.  
    Considering the widespread distribution of this system, it is difficult to determine the locations to which the contents that may contain Personal Information of the User are transferred.
    
    #### Cloudflare (Cloudflare Inc.)
    
    Cloudflare is a traffic optimization and distribution service provided by Cloudflare Inc.  
    The way Cloudflare is integrated means that it filters all the traffic through leadconvertpro.com, i.e., communication between leadconvertpro.com and the User's browser, while also allowing analytical data from leadconvertpro.com to be collected.
    
    Personal Data processed: Tracker; various types of Data as specified in the privacy policy of the service.
    
    Place of processing: United States – [Privacy Policy](https://www.cloudflare.com/privacypolicy/).
    
    Category of Personal Information collected according to the CCPA: internet or other electronic network activity information.
    
    This processing constitutes:
    
    * a Sale in California
    
    #### Sucuri CloudProxy (Sucuri, Inc.)
    
    Sucuri CloudProxy is a traffic optimization and distribution service provided by Sucuri, Inc.  
    The way Sucuri CloudProxy is integrated means that it filters all the traffic through leadconvertpro.com, i.e., communication between leadconvertpro.com and the User's browser, while also allowing analytical data from leadconvertpro.com to be collected.
    
    Personal Data processed: various types of Data as specified in the privacy policy of the service.
    
    Place of processing: United States – [Privacy Policy](https://sucuri.net/privacy/).
    
    Category of Personal Information collected according to the CCPA: internet or other electronic network activity information.
    
    This processing constitutes:
    
    * a Sale in California

Information on opting out of interest-based advertising
-------------------------------------------------------

In addition to any opt-out feature provided by any of the services listed in this document, Users may learn more on how to generally opt out of interest-based advertising within the dedicated section of the Cookie Policy.

Cookie Policy
-------------

Leadconvertpro.com uses Trackers. To learn more, Users may consult the [Cookie Policy](https://www.iubenda.com/privacy-policy/13075706/cookie-policy "Cookie Policy").

Further Information for Users in the European Union
---------------------------------------------------

This section applies to all Users in the European Union, according to the General Data Protection Regulation (the “GDPR”), and, for such Users, supersedes any other possibly divergent or conflicting information contained in the privacy policy. Further details regarding the categories of Data processed, the purposes of processing, the categories of recipients of the Personal Data, if any, and further information about Personal Data can be found in **the section titled “Detailed information on the processing of Personal Data” within this document**.

### Legal basis of processing

The Owner may process Personal Data relating to Users if one of the following applies:

* Users have given their consent for one or more specific purposes.
* provision of Data is necessary for the performance of an agreement with the User and/or for any pre-contractual obligations thereof;
* processing is necessary for compliance with a legal obligation to which the Owner is subject;
* processing is related to a task that is carried out in the public interest or in the exercise of official authority vested in the Owner;
* processing is necessary for the purposes of the legitimate interests pursued by the Owner or by a third party.

In any case, the Owner will gladly help to clarify the specific legal basis that applies to the processing, and in particular whether the provision of Personal Data is a statutory or contractual requirement, or a requirement necessary to enter into a contract.

### Further information about retention time

Unless specified otherwise in this document, Personal Data shall be processed and stored for as long as required by the purpose they have been collected for and may be retained for longer due to applicable legal obligation or based on the Users’ consent.

Therefore:

* Personal Data collected for purposes related to the performance of a contract between the Owner and the User shall be retained until such contract has been fully performed.
* Personal Data collected for the purposes of the Owner’s legitimate interests shall be retained as long as needed to fulfill such purposes. Users may find specific information regarding the legitimate interests pursued by the Owner within the relevant sections of this document or by contacting the Owner.

The Owner may be allowed to retain Personal Data for a longer period whenever the User has given consent to such processing, as long as such consent is not withdrawn. Furthermore, the Owner may be obliged to retain Personal Data for a longer period whenever required to fulfil a legal obligation or upon order of an authority.  
  
Once the retention period expires, Personal Data shall be deleted. Therefore, the right of access, the right to erasure, the right to rectification and the right to data portability cannot be enforced after expiration of the retention period.

### The rights of Users based on the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR)

Users may exercise certain rights regarding their Data processed by the Owner.

In particular, Users have the right to do the following, to the extent permitted by law:

* **Withdraw their consent at any time.** Users have the right to withdraw consent where they have previously given their consent to the processing of their Personal Data.
* **Object to processing of their Data.** Users have the right to object to the processing of their Data if the processing is carried out on a legal basis other than consent.
* **Access their Data.** Users have the right to learn if Data is being processed by the Owner, obtain disclosure regarding certain aspects of the processing and obtain a copy of the Data undergoing processing.
* **Verify and seek rectification.** Users have the right to verify the accuracy of their Data and ask for it to be updated or corrected.
* **Restrict the processing of their Data.** Users have the right to restrict the processing of their Data. In this case, the Owner will not process their Data for any purpose other than storing it.
* **Have their Personal Data deleted or otherwise removed.** Users have the right to obtain the erasure of their Data from the Owner.
* **Receive their Data and have it transferred to another controller.** Users have the right to receive their Data in a structured, commonly used and machine readable format and, if technically feasible, to have it transmitted to another controller without any hindrance.
* **Lodge a complaint.** Users have the right to bring a claim before their competent data protection authority.

Users are also entitled to learn about the legal basis for Data transfers abroad including to any international organization governed by public international law or set up by two or more countries, such as the UN, and about the security measures taken by the Owner to safeguard their Data.

#### Details about the right to object to processing

**Where Personal Data is processed for a public interest, in the exercise of an official authority vested in the Owner or for the purposes of the legitimate interests pursued by the Owner, Users may object to such processing by providing a ground related to their particular situation to justify the objection.**

**Users must know that, however, should their Personal Data be processed for direct marketing purposes, they can object to that processing at any time, free of charge and without providing any justification. Where the User objects to processing for direct marketing purposes, the Personal Data will no longer be processed for such purposes. To learn whether the Owner is processing Personal Data for direct marketing purposes, Users may refer to the relevant sections of this document.**

#### How to exercise these rights

Any requests to exercise User rights can be directed to the Owner through the contact details provided in this document. Such requests are free of charge and will be answered by the Owner as early as possible and always within one month, providing Users with the information required by law. Any rectification or erasure of Personal Data or restriction of processing will be communicated by the Owner to each recipient, if any, to whom the Personal Data has been disclosed unless this proves impossible or involves disproportionate effort. At the Users’ request, the Owner will inform them about those recipients.

### Transfer of Personal Data outside of the European Union

#### Data transfer abroad based on consent

If this is the legal basis, Personal Data of Users shall be transferred from the EU to third countries only if the User has explicitly consented to such transfer, after having been informed of the possible risks due to the absence of an adequacy decision and appropriate safeguards.  
In such cases, the Owner shall inform Users appropriately and collect their explicit consent via leadconvertpro.com.

### Transfer of Personal Data outside of the United Kingdom

#### Data transfer abroad based on consent (UK)

If this is the legal basis, Personal Data of Users shall be transferred from the UK to third countries only if the User has explicitly consented to such transfer, after having been informed of the possible risks due to the absence of an adequacy decision and appropriate safeguards.

In such cases, the Owner shall inform Users appropriately and collect their explicit consent via leadconvertpro.com.

Further information for Users in the United States
--------------------------------------------------

This part of the document integrates with and supplements the information contained in the rest of the privacy policy and is provided by the business running leadconvertpro.com and, if the case may be, its parent, subsidiaries and affiliates (for the purposes of this section referred to collectively as “we”, “us”, “our”).

The information contained in this section applies to all Users (Users are referred to below, simply as “you”, “your”, “yours”), who are residents in the following states: **California, Virginia, Colorado, Connecticut, Utah, Texas, Oregon, Nevada, Delaware, Iowa, New Hampshire, New Jersey, Nebraska and Montana.**

For such Users, this information supersedes any other possibly divergent or conflicting provisions contained in the privacy policy.

This part of the document uses the term Personal Information (and Sensitive Personal Information).

### Notice at collection

The following Notice at collection provides you with timely notice about the **categories of Personal Information collected or disclosed in the past 12 months** so that you can exercise meaningful control over our use of that Information.

_While such categorization of Personal Information is mainly based on California privacy laws, it can also be helpful for anyone who is not a California resident to get a general idea of what types of Personal Information are collected._

* ### Identifiers
    
    **Personal Information collected or disclosed:** first name, last name, phone number, company name, physical address, country, state, email address, ZIP/Postal code, city, website, various types of Data as specified in the privacy policy of the service, Tracker, Usage Data, billing address, Data communicated while using the service, unique device identifiers for advertising (Google Advertiser ID or IDFA, for example), date of birth, gender, profession, geographic position, purchase history, device information, screenshots, workplace, picture, User ID
    
    **Sensitive Personal Information collected or disclosed ℹ️:** payment info, marital status, username, password, VAT Number
    
    **Purposes:**
    
    * Contacting the User
    * Platform services and hosting
    * Displaying content from external platforms
    * Remarketing and behavioral targeting
    * Advertising
    * Managing data collection and online surveys
    * Analytics
    * Connecting Data
    * Content commenting
    * Handling payments
    * Managing contacts and sending messages
    * Handling activities related to productivity
    * Social features
    
    **Retention period:** for the time necessary to fulfill the purpose
    
    **Sold or Shared ℹ️:** Yes
    
    **Targeted Advertising: ℹ️:** Yes
    
    **Third-parties:** Automattic Inc., Facebook, Inc., Google LLC, Zapier, Inc., PayPal Inc., Stripe Inc, Twilio, Inc.
    
    **Service providers or contractors:** leadconvertpro.com
    
* ### Commercial information
    
    **Personal Information collected or disclosed:** first name, last name, phone number, company name, physical address, country, state, email address, ZIP/Postal code, city, website, various types of Data as specified in the privacy policy of the service, Tracker, Usage Data, billing address, Data communicated while using the service, date of birth, gender, profession, geographic position, purchase history, device information, screenshots, workplace, picture
    
    **Sensitive Personal Information collected or disclosed ℹ️:** payment info, marital status, username, password, VAT Number
    
    **Purposes:**
    
    * Contacting the User
    * Platform services and hosting
    * Managing data collection and online surveys
    * Connecting Data
    * Handling payments
    * Handling activities related to productivity
    * Social features
    
    **Retention period:** for the time necessary to fulfill the purpose
    
    **Sold or Shared ℹ️:** Yes
    
    **Targeted Advertising: ℹ️:** Yes
    
    **Third-parties:** Automattic Inc., Facebook, Inc., Zapier, Inc., PayPal Inc., Stripe Inc, Google LLC
    
    **Service providers or contractors:** leadconvertpro.com
    
* ### Internet or other electronic network activity information
    
    **Personal Information collected or disclosed:** first name, last name, phone number, company name, physical address, country, state, email address, ZIP/Postal code, city, website, Website, Read Mailbox, Manage Pages, Video upload, Publish as Page, Pages manage posts, Pages manage instant articles, Managing Page Advertisements, Tracker, Usage Data, various types of Data as specified in the privacy policy of the service, billing address, Data communicated while using the service, various types of Data, Trackers, unique device identifiers for advertising (Google Advertiser ID or IDFA, for example), date of birth, gender, profession, geographic position, purchase history, device information, screenshots, workplace, User ID
    
    **Sensitive Personal Information collected or disclosed ℹ️:** payment info, marital status, username, password, VAT Number
    
    **Purposes:**
    
    * Contacting the User
    * Access to third-party accounts
    * Interaction with external social networks and platforms
    * Analytics
    * Displaying content from external platforms
    * Tag Management
    * Platform services and hosting
    * Registration and authentication
    * Remarketing and behavioral targeting
    * Advertising
    * Managing data collection and online surveys
    * Interaction with live chat platforms
    * Connecting Data
    * Data transfer outside of the UK
    * Data transfer outside the EU
    * Handling payments
    * Heat mapping and session recording
    * Hosting and backend infrastructure
    * Handling activities related to productivity
    * Social features
    * SPAM protection
    * Traffic optimization and distribution
    
    **Retention period:** for the time necessary to fulfill the purpose
    
    **Sold or Shared ℹ️:** Yes
    
    **Targeted Advertising: ℹ️:** Yes
    
    **Third-parties:** Facebook, Inc., Google LLC, LinkedIn Corporation, X Corp., Automattic Inc., Meta Platforms, Inc., Sharethis Inc., Zapier, Inc., PayPal Inc., Stripe Inc, Hotjar Ltd., iubenda srl, Linode, LLC., Cloudflare Inc., Sucuri, Inc.
    
    **Service providers or contractors:** leadconvertpro.com
    
* ### Audio, electronic, visual, thermal, olfactory, or similar information
    
    **Personal Information collected or disclosed:** Website, Read Mailbox, Manage Pages, Video upload, Publish as Page, Pages manage posts, Pages manage instant articles, Managing Page Advertisements, first name, last name, physical address, gender, phone number, email address, geographic position, profession, company name, country, state, picture, city
    
    **Sensitive Personal Information collected or disclosed ℹ️:** username
    
    **Purposes:**
    
    * Access to third-party accounts
    * Social features
    
    **Retention period:** for the time necessary to fulfill the purpose
    
    **Sold or Shared ℹ️:** Yes
    
    **Targeted Advertising: ℹ️:** Yes
    
    **Third-parties:** Facebook, Inc.
    
    **Service providers or contractors:** leadconvertpro.com
    
* ### Biometric information
    
    **Personal Information collected or disclosed:** Tracker, Usage Data, first name, last name, email address, date of birth, physical address, city, country, phone number, ZIP/Postal code, gender, state, company name, profession, Data communicated while using the service, geographic position, picture
    
    **Sensitive Personal Information collected or disclosed ℹ️:** marital status, username
    
    **Purposes:**
    
    * Managing data collection and online surveys
    * Social features
    
    **Retention period:** for the time necessary to fulfill the purpose
    
    **Sold or Shared ℹ️:** Yes
    
    **Targeted Advertising: ℹ️:** Yes
    
    **Third-parties:** Facebook, Inc.
    
    **Service providers or contractors:** leadconvertpro.com
    
* ### Employment related information
    
    **Personal Information collected or disclosed:** Tracker, Usage Data, first name, last name, email address, date of birth, physical address, city, country, phone number, ZIP/Postal code, gender, state, company name, profession, Data communicated while using the service, geographic position, screenshots, workplace, picture
    
    **Sensitive Personal Information collected or disclosed ℹ️:** marital status, username, password, VAT Number
    
    **Purposes:**
    
    * Managing data collection and online surveys
    * Handling activities related to productivity
    * Social features
    
    **Retention period:** for the time necessary to fulfill the purpose
    
    **Sold or Shared ℹ️:** Yes
    
    **Targeted Advertising: ℹ️:** Yes
    
    **Third-parties:** Facebook, Inc., Google LLC
    
    **Service providers or contractors:** leadconvertpro.com
    
* ### Inferences drawn from other personal information
    
    **Personal Information collected or disclosed:** Tracker, Usage Data, first name, last name, email address, date of birth, physical address, city, country, phone number, ZIP/Postal code, gender, state, company name, profession, Data communicated while using the service
    
    **Sensitive Personal Information collected or disclosed ℹ️:** marital status
    
    **Purposes:**
    
    * Managing data collection and online surveys
    
    **Retention period:** for the time necessary to fulfill the purpose
    
    **Sold or Shared ℹ️:** Yes
    
    **Targeted Advertising: ℹ️:** Yes
    
    **Third-parties:** Facebook, Inc.
    
* ### Geolocation data
    
    **Personal Information collected or disclosed:** Tracker, first name, last name, company name, email address, country, city, geographic position, phone number, ZIP/Postal code, Data communicated while using the service, date of birth, physical address, screenshots, workplace, gender, profession, state, picture
    
    **Sensitive Personal Information collected or disclosed ℹ️:** username, password, VAT Number
    
    **Purposes:**
    
    * Connecting Data
    * Handling activities related to productivity
    * Social features
    
    **Retention period:** for the time necessary to fulfill the purpose
    
    **Sold or Shared ℹ️:** Yes
    
    **Targeted Advertising: ℹ️:** Yes
    
    **Third-parties:** Zapier, Inc., Google LLC
    
    **Service providers or contractors:** leadconvertpro.com

ℹ️ You can read the definitions of these concepts inside the “[Definitions and legal references section](#definitions_and_legal_references)” of the privacy policy.

**To know more about your rights in particular to opt out of certain processing activities and to limit the use of your sensitive personal information (“Limit the Use of My Sensitive Personal Information”) you can refer to the “[Your privacy rights under US state laws](#privacy_rights_under_us_state_laws)” section of our privacy policy.**

For more details on the collection of Personal Information, please read the section “[Detailed information on the processing of Personal Data](#data_processing_detailed_info)” of our privacy policy.

We won’t process your Information for unexpected purposes, or for purposes that are not reasonably necessary to and compatible with the purposes originally disclosed, without your consent.

### What are the sources of the Personal Information we collect?

We collect the above-mentioned categories of Personal Information, either directly or indirectly, from you when you use leadconvertpro.com.

For example, you directly provide your Personal Information when you submit requests via any forms on leadconvertpro.com. You also provide Personal Information indirectly when you navigate leadconvertpro.com, as Personal Information about you is automatically observed and collected.

Finally, we may collect your Personal Information from third parties that work with us in connection with the Service or with the functioning of leadconvertpro.com and features thereof.

### Your privacy rights under US state laws

You may exercise certain rights regarding your Personal Information. In particular, to the extent permitted by applicable law, you have:

* **the right to access Personal Information: the right to know.** You have the right to request that we confirm whether or not we are processing your Personal Information. You also have the right to access such Personal Information;
* **the right to correct inaccurate Personal Information.** You have the right to request that we correct any inaccurate Personal Information we maintain about you;
* **the right to request the deletion of your Personal Information.** You have the right to request that we delete any of your Personal Information;
* **the right to obtain a copy of your Personal Information.** We will provide your Personal Information in a portable and usable format that allows you to transfer data easily to another entity – provided that this is technically feasible;
* **the right to opt out from the Sale of your Personal Information;** We will not discriminate against you for exercising your privacy rights.
* **the right to non-discrimination.**

#### Additional rights for Users residing in California

In addition to the rights listed above common to all Users in the United States, as a User residing in California, you have

* **The right to opt out of the Sharing of your Personal Information** for cross-context behavioral advertising;
* **The right to request to limit our use or disclosure of your Sensitive Personal Information** to only that which is necessary to perform the services or provide the goods, as is reasonably expected by an average consumer. Please note that certain exceptions outlined in the law may apply, such as, when the collection and processing of Sensitive Personal Information is necessary to verify or maintain the quality or safety of our service.

#### Additional rights for Users residing in Virginia, Colorado, Connecticut, Texas, Oregon, Nevada, Delaware, Iowa, New Hampshire, New Jersey, Nebraska and Montana

In addition to the rights listed above common to all Users in the United States, as a User residing in Virginia, Colorado, Connecticut, Texas, Oregon, Nevada, Delaware, Iowa, New Hampshire, New Jersey, Nebraska and Montana you have

* **The right to opt out of** the processing of your personal information for **Targeted Advertising or profiling** in furtherance of decisions that produce legal or similarly significant effects concerning you;
* **The right to freely give, deny or withdraw your consent for the processing of your Sensitive Personal Information.** Please note that certain exceptions outlined in the law may apply, such as, but not limited to, when the collection and processing of Sensitive Personal Information is necessary for the provision of a product or service specifically requested by the consumer.

#### Additional rights for users residing in Utah and Iowa

In addition to the rights listed above common to all Users in the United States, as a User residing in Utah and Iowa, you have

* **The right to opt out of** the processing of your Personal Information for **Targeted Advertising**;
* **The right to opt out of the processing of your Sensitive Personal Information.** Please note that certain exceptions outlined in the law may apply, such as, but not limited to, when the collection and processing of Sensitive Personal Information is necessary for the provision of a product or service specifically requested by the consumer.

### How to exercise your privacy rights under US state laws

To exercise the rights described above, you need to submit your request to us by contacting us via the contact details provided in this document.

For us to respond to your request, we must know who you are. We will not respond to any request if we are unable to verify your identity and therefore confirm the Personal Information in our possession relates to you. You are not required to create an account with us to submit your request. We will use any Personal Information collected from you in connection with the verification of your request solely for verification and shall not further disclose the Personal Information, retain it longer than necessary for purposes of verification, or use it for unrelated purposes.

If you are an adult, you can make a request on behalf of a child under your parental authority.

#### How to exercise your rights to opt out

In addition to what is stated above, to exercise your right to opt-out of Sale or Sharing and Targeted Advertising you can also use the privacy choices link provided on leadconvertpro.com.

If you want to submit requests to opt out of Sale or Sharing and Targeted Advertising activities via a user-enabled **global privacy control**, such as for example the Global Privacy Control (“[GPC](https://globalprivacycontrol.org/)”), you are free to do so and we will abide by such request in a frictionless manner.

#### How and when we are expected to handle your request

We will respond to your request without undue delay, but in all cases within the timeframe required by applicable law. Should we need more time, we will explain to you the reasons why, and how much more time we need.

Should we deny your request, we will explain to you the reasons behind our denial (where envisaged by applicable law you may then contact the relevant authority to submit a complaint).

We do not charge a fee to process or respond to your request unless such request is manifestly unfounded or excessive and in all other cases where it is permitted by the applicable law. In such cases, we may charge a reasonable fee or refuse to act on the request. In either case, we will communicate our choices and explain the reasons behind them.

Additional information about Data collection and processing
-----------------------------------------------------------

### Legal action

The User's Personal Data may be used for legal purposes by the Owner in Court or in the stages leading to possible legal action arising from improper use of leadconvertpro.com or the related Services.  
The User declares to be aware that the Owner may be required to reveal personal data upon request of public authorities.

### Additional information about User's Personal Data

In addition to the information contained in this privacy policy, leadconvertpro.com may provide the User with additional and contextual information concerning particular Services or the collection and processing of Personal Data upon request.

### System logs and maintenance

For operation and maintenance purposes, leadconvertpro.com and any third-party services may collect files that record interaction with leadconvertpro.com (System logs) or use other Personal Data (such as the IP Address) for this purpose.

### Information not contained in this policy

More details concerning the collection or processing of Personal Data may be requested from the Owner at any time. Please see the contact information at the beginning of this document.

### Changes to this privacy policy

The Owner reserves the right to make changes to this privacy policy at any time by notifying its Users on this page and possibly within leadconvertpro.com and/or - as far as technically and legally feasible - sending a notice to Users via any contact information available to the Owner. It is strongly recommended to check this page often, referring to the date of the last modification listed at the bottom.  
  
Should the changes affect processing activities performed on the basis of the User’s consent, the Owner shall collect new consent from the User, where required.

### Definitions and legal references

#### Personal Data (or Data) / Personal Information (or Information)

Any information that directly, indirectly, or in connection with other information — including a personal identification number — allows for the identification or identifiability of a natural person.

#### Sensitive Personal Information

Sensitive Personal Information means any Personal Information that is not publicly available and reveals information considered sensitive according to the applicable privacy law.

#### Usage Data

Information collected automatically through leadconvertpro.com (or third-party services employed in leadconvertpro.com), which can include: the IP addresses or domain names of the computers utilized by the Users who use leadconvertpro.com, the URI addresses (Uniform Resource Identifier), the time of the request, the method utilized to submit the request to the server, the size of the file received in response, the numerical code indicating the status of the server's answer (successful outcome, error, etc.), the country of origin, the features of the browser and the operating system utilized by the User, the various time details per visit (e.g., the time spent on each page within the Application) and the details about the path followed within the Application with special reference to the sequence of pages visited, and other parameters about the device operating system and/or the User's IT environment.

#### User

The individual using leadconvertpro.com who, unless otherwise specified, coincides with the Data Subject.

#### Data Subject

The natural person to whom the Personal Data refers.

#### Data Processor (or Processor)

The natural or legal person, public authority, agency or other body which processes Personal Data on behalf of the Controller, as described in this privacy policy.

#### Data Controller (or Owner)

The natural or legal person, public authority, agency or other body which, alone or jointly with others, determines the purposes and means of the processing of Personal Data, including the security measures concerning the operation and use of leadconvertpro.com. The Data Controller, unless otherwise specified, is the Owner of leadconvertpro.com.

#### leadconvertpro.com (or this Application)

The means by which the Personal Data of the User is collected and processed.

#### Service

The service provided by leadconvertpro.com as described in the relative terms (if available) and on this site/application.

#### Sale

Sale means any exchange of Personal Information by the Owner to **a third party, for monetary or other valuable consideration**, as defined by the applicable privacy US state law. Please note that the exchange of Personal Information with a service provider pursuant to a written contract that meets the requirements set by the applicable law, does not constitute a Sale of your Personal Information.

#### Sharing

Sharing means any sharing, renting, releasing, disclosing, disseminating, making available, transferring, or otherwise communicating orally, in writing, or by electronic or other means, a consumer's Personal Information by the business to a **third party for cross-context behavioral advertising**, whether for monetary or other valuable consideration, including transactions between a business and a third party for cross-context behavioral advertising for the benefit of a business in which no money is exchanged, as defined by the California privacy laws. Please note that the exchange of Personal Information with a service provider pursuant to a written contract that meets the requirements set by the California privacy laws, does not constitute sharing of your Personal Information.

#### Targeted advertising

Targeted advertising means displaying advertisements to a consumer where the advertisement is selected based on Personal Information obtained from that consumer’s activities over time and across nonaffiliated websites or online applications to predict such consumer’s preferences or interests, as defined by the applicable privacy US state law.

#### European Union (or EU)

Unless otherwise specified, all references made within this document to the European Union include all current member states to the European Union and the European Economic Area.

#### Cookie

Cookies are Trackers consisting of small sets of data stored in the User's browser.

#### Tracker

Tracker indicates any technology - e.g Cookies, unique identifiers, web beacons, embedded scripts, e-tags and fingerprinting - that enables the tracking of Users, for example by accessing or storing information on the User’s device.

* * *

#### Legal information

This privacy statement has been prepared based on provisions of multiple legislations.

This privacy policy relates solely to leadconvertpro.com, if not stated otherwise within this document.

Latest update: March 08, 2024

[iubenda](https://www.iubenda.com/en/privacy-and-cookie-policy-generator "iubenda - Privacy Policy generator") hosts this content and only collects [the Personal Data strictly necessary](https://www.iubenda.com/privacy-policy/65675001) for it to be provided.
